A Guide to the Tredegar Iron Works Records, 1801-1957
Library of Virginia
- Series III. Production and Labor Records, 1843-1957 (bulk 1870-1930), Extent: 109.7 cu. ft. (134 boxes and 26 volumes on shelf). (Box 152-171 and 1234-1337)
  - Payroll ledger, 1923-1924, Bar mill (Box 1241)
  - Payroll ledger, 1923 May-December, Bar mill (Box 1242)
  - Payroll ledger, 1923, Foundry (Box 1243)
  - Payroll ledger, 1923 December-1924 June, Horseshoe (Box 1244)
  - Payroll ledger, 1924 January-June (Box 1245)
  - Payroll ledger, 1925 October-1926 January (Box 1246)
  - Payroll ledger, 1926 January-March (Box 1247)
  - Payroll ledger, 1927 August-November (Box 1248)
  - Payroll ledger, 1927 November-1928 February (Box 1249)
  - Payroll ledger, 1928 February-April (Box 1250)
  - Payroll ledger, 1928 April-June (Box 1251)
  - Payroll ledger, 1928 June-October (Box 1252)
  - Payroll ledger, 1928 October-December (Box 1253)
  - Payroll ledger, 1928 December-1929 April (Box 1254)
  - Payroll ledger, 1929 April-July (Box 1255)
  - Payroll ledger, 1929 August-November (Box 1256)
  - Payroll ledger, 1929 November-1930 January (Box 1257)
  - Payroll ledger, 1930 January-April (Box 1258)
  - Payroll ledger, 1930 May-August (Box 1259)
  - Payroll ledger, 1930 September-1931 January (Box 1260)
  - Payroll ledger, 1931 January-June (Box 1261)
  - Payroll ledger, 1931 June-September (Box 1262)
  - Payroll ledger, 1931 September-December (Box 1263)
  - Payroll ledger, 1932 January-February (Box 1264)
  - Payroll ledger, 1932 February-May (Box 1265)
  - Payroll ledger, 1932 May-December (Box 1266)
  - Payroll ledger, 1933 January-November (Box 1267)
  - Payroll ledger, 1933 November-1934 April (Box 1268)
  - Payroll ledger, 1934 April-June (Box 1269)
  - Payroll ledger, 1934 July-December (Box 1270)
  - Payroll ledger, 1934 December-1935 July (Box 1271)
  - Payroll ledger, 1935 July-December (Box 1272)
  - Payroll ledger, 1936 January-March DAMAGED- DO NOT SERVE (Box 1273)
  - Payroll ledger, 1936 April-June DAMAGED- DO NOT SERVE (Box 1274)
  - Payroll ledger, 1936 July-September DAMAGED- DO NOT SERVE (Box 1275)
  - Payroll ledger, 1936 October-December DAMAGED- DO NOT SERVE (Box 1276)
  - Payroll ledger, 1937 January-March (Box-folder 1277)
  - Payroll ledger, 1937 March-June (Box 1278)
  - Payroll ledger, 1937 July-September DAMAGED- DO NOT SERVE (Box 1279)
  - Payroll ledger, 1937 October-December DAMAGED- DO NOT SERVE (Box 1280)
  - Payroll ledger, 1938 January-February (Box 1281)
  - Payroll ledger, 1938 March-May (Box 1282)
  - Payroll ledger, 1938 June-September (Box 1283)
  - Payroll ledger, 1938 October-December (Box 1284)
  - Payroll ledger, 1939 January-April (Box 1285)
  - Payroll ledger, 1939 May-August (Box 1286)
  - Payroll ledger, 1939 September-December (Box 1287)
  - Payroll ledger, 1940 January-May (Box 1288)
  - Payroll ledger, 1940 June-September (Box 1289)
  - Payroll ledger, 1940 September-December (Box 1290)
  - Payroll ledger, 1941 January-March (Box 1291)
  - Payroll ledger, 1941 April-June (Box 1292)
  - Payroll ledger, 1941 July-September (Box 1293)
  - Payroll ledger, 1941 October-December (Box 1294)
  - Payroll ledger, 1942 January-April (Box 1295)
  - Payroll ledger, 1942 April-June (Box 1296)
  - Payroll ledger, 1942 June-August (Box 1297)
  - Payroll ledger, 1942 September-October (Box 1298)
  - Payroll ledger, 1942 November-December (Box 1299)
  - Payroll ledger, 1943 January-February (Box 1300)
  - Payroll ledger, 1943 March-April (Box 1301)
  - Payroll ledger, 1943 May-June (Box 1302)
  - Payroll ledger, 1943 June-July (Box 1303)
  - Payroll ledger, 1943 July-October (Box 1303a)
  - Payroll ledger, 1943 October-1944 January (Box 1304)
  - Payroll ledger, 1944 January-February (Box 1305)
  - Payroll ledger, 1944 March-April (Box 1306)
  - Payroll ledger, 1944 May-June (Box 1307)
  - Payroll ledger, 1944 July-September (Box 1308)
  - Payroll ledger, 1944 October-December (Box 1309)
  - Payroll ledger, 1944 December-1945 April (Box 1310)
  - Payroll ledger, 1945 April-June (Box 1311)
  - Payroll ledger, 1945 July-September (Box 1312)
  - Payroll ledger, 1945 October-December (Box 1313)
  - Payroll ledger, 1946 January-June (Box 1314)
  - Payroll ledger, 1946 July-December (Box 1315)
  - Payroll ledger, 1947 January-August (Box 1316)
  - Payroll ledger, 1947 August-1948 March (Box 1317)
  - Payroll ledger, 1948 March-July (Box 1318)
  - Payroll ledger, 1948 July-December (Box 1319)
  - Payroll ledger, 1949 January-June (Box 1320)
  - Payroll ledger, 1949 July-December (Box 1321)
  - Payroll ledger, 1950 January-May (Box 1322)
  - Payroll ledger, 1950 June-December (Box 1323)
  - Payroll ledger, 1951 January-July (Box 1324)
  - Payroll ledger, 1951 July-1952 March (Box 1325)
  - Payroll ledger, 1952 March-August (Box 1326)
  - Payroll ledger, 1952 August-December (Box 1327)
  - Payroll ledger, 1953 January-June (Box 1328)
  - Payroll ledger, 1953 July-December (Box 1329)
  - Payroll ledger, 1954 January-June (Box 1330)
  - Payroll ledger, 1954 July-December (Box 1331)
  - Payroll ledger, 1954 December-1955 June (Box 1332)
  - Payroll ledger, 1955 June-October (Box 1333)
  - Payroll ledger, 1955 October-1956 April (Box 1334)
  - Payroll ledger, 1956 April-December (Box 1335)
  - Payroll ledger, 1957 January-June (Box 1336)
  - Payroll distribution ledger, 1946 January-1957 June (Box 1337)
  - Box numbering system returns to normal. Starts at Box No. 165.
  - Time book, Machine shop, 1854 July-1855 May (Box 165)
  - Time book, Machine shop, 1855 March-August (Box 165)
  - Time book, 1875 July-1877 February (Box 165)
  - Time book, Smith shop, 1876 February-1880 December (Box 166)
  - Time book, Rolling mill, spike mill, and steam forge, 1881 (Box 166)
  - Time book, Machine shop, 1883 (Box 166)
  - Time book, 1883 January21-1887 July 10 (Box 166)
  - Time book, 1892 October 1-1893 August 31 (Box 167)
  - Time book, Rolling mill, 1871 February 16-1871 December 19 (Volume on shelf)
  - Time book, Machine shop, 1893 September 1-1894 June 30 (Volume on shelf)
  - Time book, Boiler shop, 1895 June 1-1898 February 28 (Volume on shelf)
  - Time book, 1897 July-1900 April (Volume on shelf)
  - Units produced, Castings, 1843 May-1849 September (Box 168)
  - Units produced, Ten inch train mill spikes and kegs, 1870 December 20-1872 December 18 (Box 168)
  - Units produced, Eight inch train mill spikes and kegs, 1871 May 17-1872 March 25 (Box 168)
  - Units produced, Box cars and gondolas, 1872 January-1880 September (Box 169)
  - Units produced, 1872 March 26-1873 April 30 (Box 169)
  - Units produced, Brass and iron castings, 1875 July 1-1888 June 1 (Box 169)
  - Units produced, Production records of individual heaters and straighteners, 1868 July-1872 December (Box 169a)
  - Units produced, Spike mill, 1879 June-1881 December (Volume on shelf)
  - Units produced, Spike mill, 1896 October 26-1902 August (Volume on shelf)
  - Units produced, 1893 December 3-1898 March (Box 170)
  - Units produced, Car wheels, 1895 March 5-1906 October 23 (Box 170)
  - Units produced, Ordnance, 1918 (Box 170)
  - Units produced, 1888 June 2-1890 August 18 (Box 171)
  - Units produced, Horse shoes, 1899 March 12-1903 September 19 (Volume on shelf)
  - Units produced, Horse shoes, 1900 May-1904 October (Volume on shelf)
  - Units produced, Horse shoes, 1901 October 12-1902 April 30 (Volume on shelf)
  - Units produced, Horse and mule shoes punched, 1914 July 25-1915 October 16 (Box 171a)
  - Units produced, Bar mill, merchant mill, rod mill and horse shoe mill, 1924 June-1925 August (Volume on shelf)
  - Weigher's returns, 1889 March 5-1892 August 27 (Volume on shelf)
  - Weigher's returns, 1892 October 1-1894 January 31 (Volume on shelf)
  - Weigher's returns, 1894 February 1-1895 August 31 (Volume on shelf)
  - Weigher's returns, 1897 February-1898 August 31 (Volume on shelf)
  - Weigher's returns, 1898 December 1-1900 January 31 (Volume on shelf)
  - Weigher's returns, 1900 February 1-1901 August 31 (Volume on shelf)
  - Weigher's returns, 1923 December 2-1926 August 31 (Volume on shelf)
  - Weigher's returns, 1926 September 1-1930 July 31 (Volume on shelf)
  - Weigher's returns, 1930 August 4-1938 December 30 (Volume on shelf)
- Series IV. Purchasing and Receiving Records, 1861-1911, Extent: .75 cu. ft. (3 boxes). (Box 172-174)
  - Invoice book, 1867 April-1870 October (Box 172)
  - Invoice book, 1868 April-1874 August (Box 172)
  - Invoice book, 1872 July 8-1879 January 3 (Box-folder 173:1)
  - Invoice book, 1884 January 5-1886 March 19 (Box-folder 173:2)
  - Invoice book, 1909 June 6-1911 December 30 (Box-folder 173:3)
  - Receipt book, coal, 1879-1885 (use Misc. reel 5026) (Box-folder 174:1)
  - Receipt book, pig iron, 1861-1864 (use Misc. reel 5026) (Box-folder 174:2)
  - Receipt book, pig and scrap iron, 1879-1885 (use Misc. reel 5026) (Box-folder 174:3)
  - Receiving book, 1862-1865 (use Misc. reel 5026) (Box-folder 174:4)
- Series V. Sales and Shipping Records, 1843-1956 (bulk 1873-1925), Extent: 30.85 cu. ft. (32 boxes and 97 volumes on shelf). (Box 175-204)
  Volumes are alphabetically arranged to the front, followed by loose papers arranged alphabetically by title.
  - Volumes:
  - Consignment book, 1865-1874 (Box 175)
  - Contract book, 1859 July-1865 April, Pages i-viii and 1-75 (Box-folder 176:1)
  - Contract book, 1859 July-1865 April, Pages 76-135 (Box-folder 176:2)
  - Contract book, 1859 July-1865 April, Pages 135a-203 (Box-folder 176:3)
  - Contract book, 1859 July-1865 April, Pages 204-254 (Box-folder 176:4)
  - Contract book, 1865 September-1866 November 29 (Box-folder 176:5)
  - Contract book, 1867 February 5-1868 June 23 (Box-folder 176:6)
  - Contract book, 1868 May-1871 June (Box-folder 177:1)
  - Contract book, 1868 July-1870 April 26 (Box-folder 177:2)
  - Contract book, 1870 April-1880 October (Box-folder 178:1)
  - Contract book, 1892 November-1915 January (Box-folder 178:2)
  - Cost sheet book, 1924-1930 (Volume on shelf)
  - Cost sheet book, 1931-1935 (Volume on shelf)
  - Loadings, Railroad freight car, 1892 (Box 179)
  - Order books, 1853 January 1-1859 March 15. Order books, 1861 August 13-1862 November 27 (Box 180)
  - Order books, 1866 July-1871 January 11 (Box 181)
  - Order books, 1871 January 5-1871 June 17 (Box 182)
  - Order books,1876 January 18-1877 June 11 (Volume on shelf)
  - Order books, 1877 June 18-1878 November 9 (Volume on shelf)
  - Order books, 1878 November 12-1880 September 30 (Volume on shelf)
  - Order books, 1880 October-1882 December (Volume on shelf)
  - Order books, 1883 January 1-1884 December 1 (Volume on shelf)
  - Order books, 1886 September 1-1887 August 10 (Volume on shelf)
  - Order books, 1888 March 15-1889 November 8 (Volume on shelf)
  - Order books, 1889 November- 1891 September 15 (Volume on shelf)
  - Order books, 1897 May-1899 April 21 (Volume on shelf)
  - Order books, 1899 April 22-1901 April 21 (Volume on shelf)
  - Order books, 1907 May 15-1908 October 9 (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Foundry, 1854 September-1860 September (Box 183)
  - Sales books, Foundry, 1858 February-1865 September (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Foundry, 1860 November-1867 November (Box 184)
  - Sales books, Foundry, 1865 January 12-1872 December 31 (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Foundry, 1873 January-1876 January 13 (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Foundry, 1876 January-1879 August (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Foundry, 1879 September-1883 December (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Foundry, 1889 June 1-1892 September 30 (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Foundry, 1892 October 1-1895 November 30 (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Foundry, 1895 December 1-1898 April 30 (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Foundry, 1898 April 1-1900 January 31 (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Foundry, 1900 February-1901 May (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Foundry, 1901 June-1902 August (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Foundry, 1902 September-1904 January (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Foundry, 1904 February-1905 September (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Foundry, 1905 October-1907 February (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Foundry, 1907 March-1908 September (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Foundry, 1908 October-1910 May (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Foundry, 1910 June-1912 April (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Foundry, 1912 May-1913 December (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Foundry, 1914 January-1916 August (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Foundry, 1916 September-1919 February (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Foundry, 1919 March-1921 July (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Foundry, 1921 August-1923 May (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Foundry, 1923 May-1924 June (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1873 June 2-1875 August 31 (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1884 January-1889 May (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1884 April 18-1890 December (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1891 January-1892 September 30 (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1892 October 1-1894 September (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1894 October 1-1897 February (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1897 (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1897 March 1-1898 March (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1898 March-1899 March (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1899 March-1900 August (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1900 September 1-1901 December (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1902 January-1903 August (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1903 September 1-1904 October (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1904 November-1906 March (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1906 April-1907 August (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1907 September-1909 March (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1909 April-1910 May (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1910 June-1911 October (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1911 November-1913 February (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1913 March-1914 June (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1914 July-1915 September (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1915 September-1917 March (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1917 March-1919 August (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1919 August-1921 September (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1921 October-1923 June (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Horseshoe, 1923 July-1924 June (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1843 July-1846 March (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1853 September-1857 October (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1857 July 20-1859 March 30 (Box 184a)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1868 January 1-1871 December 31 (Box 184b)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1872 January-1873 May (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1875 September-1876 January (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1875 December-1880 May 31 (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1876 January-1877 September (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1877 October-1879 August (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1879 September-1880 December (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1881 January-1882 March (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1882 March-1883 December (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1884 January-1885 December (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1886 January-1887 October (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1887 November-1889 August 3 (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1889 September-1891 June (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1891 July-1893 May (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1893 June-1895 May (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1895 June-1897 August (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1897 September-1899 July (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1899 August-1900 December (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1901 May-1902 November (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1902 December-1904 July (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1904 August-1906 April (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1906 May-1907 October (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1907 October-1909 September (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1909 October-1911 June (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1911 July-1913 May (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1913 June-1915 August (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1915 September-1917 April (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1917 May-1918 December (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, 1918 June-1922 March (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, Bar mill, 1919 January-1921 July (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales books, Rolling mill, Bar mill, 1921 August-1923 December (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales book, Rolling mill, Spike mill, 1922 April-1924 June (Volume on shelf)
  - Sales book, Rolling mill, Bar mill, 1924 January-June (Volume on shelf)
  - Shipment of Sash Weights, 1896 February-1896 December 31 (Volume on shelf)
  - Ticket books, 1847 May-1854 February (Box 185)
  - Ticket books, 1858 August 9-1859 August 17 (Box 185)
  - Ticket books, 1859 September 2-1863 June 18 (Box 185)
  - Ticket books, 1862 March-1863 January (Box 185)
  - Ticket books, 1861 August 6-1863 June 18 (Box 186)
  - Ticket books, 1864 January-1865 August 31 (Box 186)
  - Ticket books, 1866 September 15-1867 March 2 (Box 187)
  - Ticket books, 1868 November 14-1869 January 30 (Box 187)
  - Ticket books, 1873 August 23-1873 September 3 (Box 188)
  - Ticket books, 1875 May 3-1875 October 15 (Box 188)
  - Ticket books, 1876 December 7-1878 November 13 (Box 189)
  - Ticket books, 1898 December 2-1899 March 24 (Box 189)
  - Ticket books, 1899 May 18-1900 January 9 (Box 190)
  - Ticket books, 1899 November 18-1900 July 18 (Box 190)
  - Ticket books, 1901 June 4-1902 February 7 (Box 191)
  - Ticket books, 1907 April 4-1908 February 6 (Box 192)
  - Loose papers:
  - Bids submitted, 1920-1925 (Box-folder 193:1)
  - Bids submitted, 1926-1930 (Box-folder 193:2)
  - Bids submitted, 1951-1952 November (Box-folder 193:3)
  - Bids submitted, 1952 November-December (Box-folder 193:4)
  - Bids submitted, Shot, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 193:5)
  - Bids submitted, Steel forging for shell stock, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 193:6)
  - Bids submitted, Shell (M335), 1953 (Box-folder 194:1)
  - Bids submitted, Shell (M744), 1953 (Box-folder 194:2)
  - Bids submitted, Transverse stiffener, 1953 (Box-folder 194:3)
  - Bids submitted, Maintenance platform, 1954 (Box-folder 194:4)
  - Bids submitted, Maintenance stands, 1954 (Box-folder 194:5)
  - Bids submitted, Mine anchors, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 194:6)
  - Bids submitted, 1954-1956 (Box-folder 194:7)
  - Cleaning of metal surfaces for ammunitions items, 1952 (Box-folder 194:8)
  - Damage claims, 1917-1919 (Box-folder 194:9)
  - Horseshoe price lists, 1899-1901 (Box-folder 194:10)
  - Instructions to contractors, 1917-1921 (Box-folder 195:1)
  - Misc. sales agreements, 1868-1924 (Box-folder 195:2)
  - Misc. sales agreements, 1949-1954 (Box-folder 195:3)
  - Misc. specifications, 1936-1949 (Box-folder 195:4)
  - Misc. specifications, 1951-1953 (Box-folder 195:5)
  - Statement of shipments for target projectiles, 1919-1920 (Box-folder 195:6)
  - War department contracts, 1907 July 30 (Box-folder 196:1)
  - War department contracts, 1907 October 4 (Box-folder 196:2)
  - War department contracts, 1907 November 19 (Box-folder 196:3)
  - War department contracts, 1908 February 29 (Box-folder 196:4)
  - War department contracts, 1908 April 14 (Box-folder 196:5)
  - War department contracts, 1908 June 10 (Box-folder 196:6)
  - War department contracts, 1908 August 18 (Box-folder 196:7)
  - War department contracts, 1908 September 5 (Box-folder 196:8)
  - War department contracts, 1909 April 27 (Box-folder 196:9)
  - War department contracts, 1909 May 13 (Box-folder 196:10)
  - War department contracts, 1909 June 22 and 1909 August 9 (Box-folder 196:11)
  - War department contracts, 1909 October 18 (Box-folder 196:12)
  - War department contracts, 1909 October 20 (Box-folder 196:13)
  - War department contracts, 1909 December 17 (Box-folder 196:14)
  - War department contracts, 1909 December 22 (Box-folder 196:15)
  - War department contracts, 1910 March 1 (Box-folder 197:1)
  - War department contracts, 1910 April 20 (Box-folder 197:2)
  - War department contracts, 1910 April 11 (Box-folder 197:3)
  - War department contracts, 1910 December 30 (Box-folder 197:4)
  - War department contracts, 1911 May 30 (Box-folder 197:5)
  - War department contracts, 1911 June 9 (Box-folder 197:6)
  - War department contracts, 1911 December 7 (Box-folder 197:7)
  - War department contracts, 1912 February 20 (Box-folder 197:8)
  - War department contracts, 1912 March 15 (Box-folder 197:9)
  - War department contracts, 1912 April 29 (Box-folder 197:10)
  - War department contracts, 1912 May 24 (Box-folder 197:11)
  - War department contracts, 1912 July 11 (Box-folder 197:12)
  - War department contracts, 1912 September 7 (Box-folder 197:13)
  - War department contracts, 1912 November 2 (Box-folder 197:14)
  - War department contracts, 1912 November 12 (Box-folder 197:15)
  - War department contracts, 1913 March 18 (Box-folder 198:1)
  - War department contracts, 1913 June 3 (Box-folder 198:2)
  - War department contracts, 1913 July 7 (Box-folder 198:3)
  - War department contracts, 1913 July 16 (Box-folder 198:4)
  - War department contracts, 1913 September 3 (Box-folder 198:5)
  - War department contracts, 1914 January 9 (Box-folder 198:6)
  - War department contracts, 1914 April 1 (Box-folder 198:7)
  - War department contracts, 1914 August 25 (Box-folder 198:8)
  - War department contracts, 1914 September 25 (Box-folder 198:9)
  - War department contracts, 1914 November 28 (Box-folder 198:10)
  - War department contracts, 1915 March 3 (Box-folder 198:11)
  - War department contracts, 1915 March 13 (Box-folder 198:12)
  - War department contracts, 1915 June 10 (Box-folder 199:1)
  - War department contracts, 1915 September 13 (Box-folder 199:2)
  - War department contracts, 1917 January 30 (Box-folder 199:3)
  - War department contracts, 1917 March 21 (Box-folder 199:4)
  - War department contracts, 1917 April 16 (Box-folder 199:5)
  - War department contracts, 1917 May 4 (Box-folder 199:6)
  - War department contracts, 1917 May 14 (Box-folder 199:7)
  - War department contracts, 1917 May 28 (Box-folder 199:8)
  - War department contracts, 1917 August 31 (Box-folder 199:9)
  - War department contracts, 1917 September 15 (Box-folder 199:10)
  - War department contracts, 1917 September 24 (Box-folder 199:11)
  - War department contracts, 1917 October 10 (Box-folder 199:12)
  - War department contracts, 1917 November 17 (Box-folder 199:13)
  - War department contracts, 1918 February 1 (Box-folder 200:1)
  - War department contracts, 1918 February 19 (Box-folder 200:2)
  - War department contracts, 1918 February 28 (Box-folder 200:3)
  - War department contracts, 1918 March 14 (Box-folder 200:4)
  - War department contracts, 1918 April 4 (Box-folder 200:5)
  - War department contracts, 1918 May 15 (Box-folder 200:6)
  - War department contracts, 1918 May 23 (Box-folder 200:7)
  - War department contracts, 1918 June 12 (Box-folder 200:8)
  - War department contracts, 1918 June 22 (Box-folder 200:9)
  - War department contracts, 1918 June 24 (Box-folder 200:10)
  - War department contracts, 1918 June 25 (Box-folder 200:11)
  - War department contracts, 1918 July 10 (Box-folder 200:12)
  - War department contracts, 1918 July 31 (Box-folder 200:13)